WestConn Serials and Publications Catalogs, Yearbooks, View Books, Registration Booklets and Academic Journals RG 8.1
Western Connecticut State University Archives and Special Collections
WestConn Serials and Publications
1904-2008
Western Connecticut State University Archives and Special Collections
Western Connecticut State University.
RG 8.1
182
50 Linear Feet Inlcudes boxed publications and loose bound volumes.
This collection is an inventory of the yearbooks, course catalogs (with related supplements), academic journals, alumni newsletters, view books, registration booklets and other miscellany published by WestConn.
15 linear feet
Provenance
Most yearbooks and catalogs were maintained as serials in the catalog.
Access Restrictions
Open for research without restrictions.
Historical/Biographical Note
Western Connecticut State University is a public state university in Danbury, Connecticut. It was founded in 1903 as the Danbury Normal School and is known as WestConn, Western and WCSU. It began as a teacher's college and has evolved to include arts and sciences, business, nursing, music performance, and social work.
Scope and Content Note
While it is difficult to determine if this collection includes all the catalogs, yearbooks and other related University publications of this kind, it provides a fairly comprehensive assemblage. Issues of the yearbook that the archive does not own are indicated in the scope note for that series.
Arrangement
The files are grouped into 6 series:
Missing Title
Unbound Course Catalogs
Bound sets and single volumes of Course Catalogs
Registration Booklets
Course Offerings - Oversize circulars
Western Matters
Yearbooks
Publications.; Universities and colleges -- Administration.; Universities and colleges -- Students.; Yearbooks.; College students.; Course Catalogs.; Danbury (Conn.); Fliers (printed matter); Danbury Normal School.; Danbury State Teachers College.; Danbury Teachers College.; Western Connecticut State College.; Western Connecticut State University.
- Unbound Course Catalogs, 54237
  - Announcement, 1905-1906; 54246 (Box A)
  - Course Catalogs, 1904-1930; 54245 (Box A)
  - Course Catalogs, 1931-1954; 54244 (Box B)
  - Course Catalogs, 1955-1969; 54243 (Box C)
  - Graduate Course Catalogs, 1964-1966; 54242 (Box D)
  - Graduate Course Catalogs, 1968-1970; 54241 (Box D)
  - Graduate Course Catalogs, 1971-1973; 54240 (Box D)
  - Graduate Course Catalogs, 1976-1978; 54239 (Box D)
  - Graduate Course Catalogs, 2000; 54238 (Box D)
- View books, handbooks, survival guides, 1980-2012
  - Student Handbook (aka Compass), 1990-2012 (Box E, Item 1-11)
    General
    11 issues
  - Survival Guide, 2002-2006 (Box E, Item 12-15)
  - Viewbook, 1980s-2000s (Box E, Item 16-31)
    Also includes: undergraduate guide to student achievement, undated; starting now, undated, for non-trad students; and 3 welcome booklets, undated, circa 2005.
- Bound sets and single volumes of Course Catalogs -, 54161
  - Danbury Normal Training School Documents, 1904-1915; 54236 (Item 1)
  - Danbury Normal School Annual Catalogues, 1933-1940; 54235 (Item 2)
  - Danbury Normal School Annual Catalogues, 1934-1940; 54234 (Item 3)
  - Danbury State Teachers College Annual Catalogs, 1938-1942; 54233 (Item 4)
  - Danbury State Teachers College Annual Catalogs (two copies), 1940-1944; 54232 (Item 5-6)
  - Danbury State Teachers College, 1942-1946; 54231 (Item 7a)
  - Danbury State Teachers College, 1944-1950; 54230 (Item 7b)
  - Danbury State Teachers College, 1944-1951; 54229 (Item 8)
  - Danbury State Teachers College, 1946-1950; 54228 (Item 9a)
  - Danbury State Teachers College, 1949-1954; 54227 (Item 9b)
  - Danbury State Teachers College, 1950-1954; 54226 (Item 9c)
  - Danbury State Teachers College Extension Program, 1952-1957; 54225 (Item 10a)
  - Danbury State Teachers College Catalogs, 1952-1961; 54224 (Item 10b)
  - Danbury State Teachers College Catalogs, 1952-1962; 54223 (Item 11)
  - Danbury State Teachers College Catalogs, 1954-1962; 54222 (Item 12)
  - Danbury State Teachers College Catalogs, 1962-1967; 54221 (Item 13)
  - Western Connecticut State College, 1961-1970; 54220 (Item 14)
  - Western Connecticut State College (includes Graduate Studies 1968-1970), 1967-1970; 54219 (Item 15)
  - Western Connecticut State College (includes Graduate Studies 1968-1970), 54218 (Item 16)
  - Western Connecticut State College, 1971-1978; 54217 (Item 17)
  - Western Connecticut State College, 1979-1982; 54216 (Item 18)
  - Western Connecticut State College, 1983-1986; 54215 (Item 19)
  - Western Connecticut State College, 1969-1970; 54214 (Item 20)
  - Western Connecticut State College, 1970-1971; 54213 (Item 21)
    General note
    2 copies
  - Western Connecticut State College, 1971-1972; 54212 (Item 22)
  - Western Connecticut State College, 1972-1973; 54211 (Item 23)
  - Western Connecticut State College, 1973; 54210 (Item 24)
  - Western Connecticut State College, 1975-1976; 54209 (Item 25)
  - Western Connecticut State College, 1976-1977; 54208 (Item 26)
  - Western Connecticut State College, 1977-1978; 54207 (Item 27)
  - Western Connecticut State College, 1978-1979; 54206 (Item 28)
  - Western Connecticut State College Graduate Division, 1978-1980; 54205 (Item 29)
  - Western Connecticut State College, 1979-1980; 54204 (Item 30)
  - Western Connecticut State College, 1980-1981; 54203 (Item 31)
  - Western Connecticut State College Graduate Division, 1980-1982; 54202 (Item 32)
  - Western Connecticut State College, 1981-1982; 54201 (Item 33)
  - Western Connecticut State College Graduate Division, 1982-1984; 54200 (Item 34)
  - Western Connecticut State University, 1983-1984; 54199 (Item 35)
  - Western Connecticut State University, 1982-1983; 54198 (Item 36)
  - Western Connecticut State University, 1984-1985; 54197 (Item 37)
  - Western Connecticut State University Graduate, 1984-1986; 54196 (Item 38)
    3 copies
  - Western Connecticut State University, 1985-1986; 54195 (Item 39)
  - Western Connecticut State University, 1986-1987; 54194 (Item 40)
  - Western Connecticut State University, 1987-1988; 54193 (Item 41)
  - Western Connecticut State University Graduate, 1986-1988; 54192 (Item 42)
  - Western Connecticut State University, 1988-1989; 54191 (Item 43)
  - Western Connecticut State University, 1989-1990; 54190 (Item 44)
  - Western Connecticut State University Graduate, 1988-1990; 54189 (Item 45)
  - Western Connecticut State University, 1990-1991; 54188 (Item 46)
  - Western Connecticut State University, 1991-1992; 54187 (Item 47)
  - Western Connecticut State University Graduate, 1990-1992; 54186 (Item 48)
  - Western Connecticut State University, 1992-1993; 54185 (Item 49)
  - Western Connecticut State University, 1993-1994; 54184 (Item 50)
  - Western Connecticut State University Graduate, 1992-1994; 54183 (Item 51)
  - Western Connecticut State University, 1994-1995; 54182 (Item 52)
  - Western Connecticut State University Graduate, 1994-1996; 54181 (Item 53)
    2 copies; NB: Spine says 1994-1995; Cover says 1994-1996
  - Western Connecticut State University, 1995-1996; 54180 (Item 54)
  - Western Connecticut State University, 1996-1997; 54179 (Item 55)
  - Western Connecticut State University, 1997-1998; 54178 (Item 56)
  - Western Connecticut State University, 1998-1999; 54177 (Item 57)
  - Western Connecticut State University Graduate, 1998-1999; 54176 (Item 58)
  - Western Connecticut State University, 1999-2000; 54175 (Item 59)
  - Western Connecticut State University Graduate, 1999-2000; 54174 (Item 60)
  - Western Connecticut State University, 2000-2001; 54173 (Item 61)
  - Western Connecticut State University Graduate, 2000-2001; 54172 (Item 62)
  - Western Connecticut State University, 2001-2002; 54171 (Item 63)
  - Western Connecticut State University Graduate, 2001-2002; 54170 (Item 64)
  - Western Connecticut State University, 2002-2003; 54169 (Item 65)
  - Western Connecticut State University Graduate, 2002-2003; 54168 (Item 66)
  - Western Connecticut State University, 2003-2004; 54167 (Item 67)
  - Western Connecticut State University Graduate, 2003-2004; 54166 (Item 68)
  - Western Connecticut State University, 2005-2006; 54165 (Item 69)
  - Western Connecticut State University Graduate, 2005-2006; 54164 (Item 70)
  - Western Connecticut State University Graduate, 2007-2008; 54163 (Item 71)
  - Western Connecticut State University, 1969-1970; 54162 (Item 72)
- Registration Booklets, 54030
  - Semesterly Extension Program booklets with mail in registration; 1956-1957 Gr, 1953-1957; 54160 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Summer Session, 1953-1959; 54159 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Summer Session, 1960-1969; 54158 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Graduate and Evening, 1966-1971; 54157 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Summer Session, 1970-1972; 54156 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Graduate and Evening, 1971-1974; 54155 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Undergraduate/Graduate, 1973; 54154 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Summer Session, 1972-1973; 54153 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Undergraduate Day and Evening: Fall 1973 - Spring 1974, 1973-1974; 54152 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Summer Session, 1974; 54151 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Undergraduate Day and Evening: Fall 1974 - Spring 1975, 1974-1975; 54150 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Spring Undergraduate, 1975-1979; 54149 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - History and Social Science: Summer 1975, Fall 1975, 54148 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Summer Session, 1975-1976; 54147 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Graduate and Evening: Fall 1975, Fall1976, 1975-1976; 54146 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - History and Social Science: Spring 1976, Summer 1976, Fall 1976, 54145 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Extended & Career Development, 1976; 54144 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Extended & Career Development: Spring/Fall 1977, 54143 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Summer Session, 1977-1978; 54142 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Graduate and Evening: Fall 1977, Fall 1979, 54141 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Summer Session, Extended & Career Development, 1977-1979; 54140 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - History and Social Science: Spring 1978, 54139 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Extended & Career Development: Spring/Fall 1978, 54138 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Training for Eco. Development: Summer 1978, 54137 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Extended & Career Development: Spring/Fall 1979, 54136 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Summer Session, 1979; 54135 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - History and English: Summer 1979, 54134 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Undergraduate: Spring 1980, 54133 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Graduate and Evening: Spring 1980, 54132 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Extended & Career Development: Spring 1980, Spring 1982, 1980-1982; 54131 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Summer Session: Summer 1980, 54130 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Undergraduate: Spring 1981, 54129 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - History: Spring 1982, 54128 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Undergraduate: Spring 1982, 54127 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Extended & Career Development: Fall 1982, 54126 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Undergraduate: Spring 1983, 54125 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Extended & Career Development: Spring 1983, 54124 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Undergraduate: Fall 1983, 54123 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Extended & Career Development: Fall 1983, Spring 1984, 1983-1984; 54122 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Undergraduate: Spring 1984, Fall 1984, 54121 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Life Long Learning: Fall 1984, 54120 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Life Long Learning: Spring 1985, 54119 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Undergraduate: Spring 1985, 54118 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Undergraduate: Fall 1985, 54117 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Life Long Learning: Fall 1985, 54116 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Life Long Learning: Spring 1986, Fall 1986, 54115 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Undergraduate: Fall 1986, 54114 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Undergraduate: Spring 1986, 54113 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Undergraduate: Spring 1987, 54112 (Box 3, Folder 11A)
  - Life Long Learning: Spring 1987, 54111 (Box 3, Folder 11B)
  - Undergraduate: Fall 1987, 54110 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Undergraduate: Spring 1988, 54109 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Undergraduate: Fall 1988, 54108 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Undergraduate: Spring 1989, 54107 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Undergraduate: Fall 1989, 54106 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Undergraduate: Spring 1990, 54105 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Undergraduate: Fall 1990, 54104 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - History: Fall 1990, Spring 1991, 54103 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Undergraduate: Spring 1991, 54102 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Undergraduate: Fall 1991, 54101 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Graduate Studies: Fall 1991, 54100 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Undergraduate: Spring 1992, 54099 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Graduate Studies: Spring 1992, 54098 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Undergraduate: Summer 1992, 54097 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Undergraduate: Fall 1992, 54096 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Graduate and Evening: Fall 1992, 54095 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Undergraduate: Spring 1993, 54094 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Undergraduate Intercession: Intercession 1993, 54093 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Summer Session: Summer 1993, 54092 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Undergraduate: Fall 1993, 54091 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Graduate and Evening, 1993; 54090 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Undergraduate: Spring 1994, 54089 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Graduate and Evening, 1994; 54088 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Graduate and Evening: Summer 1994, 54087 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Undergraduate: Fall 1994, 54086 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Graduate and Evening: Fall 1994, 54085 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Undergraduate: Spring 1995, 54084 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Graduate and Evening: Spring 1995, 54083 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Regional Adult and Continuing Education: Spring 1995, 54082 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Undergraduate: Summer 1995, 54081 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Undergraduate: Fall 1995, 54080 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Undergraduate: Spring 1996, 54079 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Undergraduate: Fall 1996, 54078 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Undergraduate: Spring 1997, 54077 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Undergraduate: Fall 1997, 54076 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Intercession: Intercession 1998, 54075 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Undergraduate: Spring 1998, 54074 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Undergraduate: Fall 1998, 54073 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Undergraduate: Spring 1999, 54072 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Undergraduate: Fall 1999, 54071 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Non-Credit: Fall 1999, 54070 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Intercession: Intercession 1999, 54069 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Undergraduate and Graduate: Spring 2000, 54068 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Non-Credit: Spring 2000, 54067 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Summer Session Graduate: Summer 2000, 54066 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Undergraduate and Graduate: Fall 2000, 54065 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Western in Waterbury: Fall 2000, 54064 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Non-Credit, 2000; 54063 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Undergraduate: Spring 2001, 54062 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Western in Waterbury: Spring 2001, 54061 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Undergraduate: Fall 2001, 54060 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Non-Credit: Fall 2001, 54059 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Undergraduate: Spring 2002, 54058 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Non-Credit: Spring 2002, 54057 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Undergraduate: Fall 2002, 54056 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Non-Credit: Fall 2002, 54055 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Intercession: Intercession 2003, 54054 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Undergraduate: Spring 2003, 54053 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Non-Credit, 2003; 54052 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Summer Session: Summer 2003, 54051 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Undergraduate and Graduate: Fall 2003, 54050 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Non-Credit, 2003; 54049 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Undergraduate: Spring 2004, 54048 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Non-Credit: Spring 2004, 54047 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Undergraduate: Summer 2004, 54046 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Graduate Studies: Summer 2004, 54045 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Undergraduate: Fall 2004, 54044 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Non-Credit: Fall 2004, 54043 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Graduate Studies: Fall 2004, 54042 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Undergraduate: Spring 2005, 54041 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Summer Session: Summer 2005, 54040 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Undergraduate: Fall 2005, 54039 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Evening Classes: Fall 2005, 54038 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Non-Credit: Fall 2005, 54037 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Non-Credit: Spring 2006, 54036 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Undergraduate: Spring 2006, 54035 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Undergraduate: Summer 2006, 54034 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Undergraduate and Graduate: Fall 2006, 54033 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Undergraduate and Evening: Fall 2006, 54032 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Undergraduate and Evening: Spring 2007, 54031 (Box 7, Folder 22)
- Course Offerings - Oversize circulars, 53969
  Missing following oversize circulars:
  Undergraduate and Graduate: Fall 1983 Undergraduate and Graduate: Fall 1994 Undergraduate and Graduate: Spring 1995 Undergraduate and Graduate: Summer 1995
  - Continuing Education and Graduate: Fall 2002, 54029 (Box OS 1, Item 1)
  - Undergraduate and Graduate: Summer 2002, 54028 (Box OS 1, Item 2)
  - Undergraduate and Graduate Evening: Spring 2002, 54027 (Box OS 1, Item 3)
  - Undergraduate: Intersession 2002, 54026 (Box OS 1, Item 3a)
    Two copies
  - Undergraduate and Graduate Evening: Fall 2001, 54025 (Box OS 1, Item 4)
  - Undergraduate and Graduate: Summer 2001, 54024 (Box OS 1, Item 5)
  - Undergraduate and Graduate Evening: Spring 2001, 54023 (Box OS 1, Item 6)
  - Undergraduate: Intercession 2001, 54022 (Box OS 1, Item 7)
  - Undergraduate and Graduate: Fall 2000, 54021 (Box OS 1, Item 8)
  - Undergraduate and Graduate: Summer 2000, 54020 (Box OS 1, Item 9)
  - Undergraduate Night: Spring 2000, 54019 (Box OS 1, Item 10)
  - Undergraduate: Intercession 2000, 54018 (Box OS 1, Item 11)
  - Extended Programs and Career Development: Fall 1980, 54017 (Box OS 2, Item 1A)
  - Extended Programs and Career Development: Spring 1981, 54016 (Box OS 2, Item 1B)
  - Undergraduate and Graduate: Summer 1982, 54015 (Box OS 2, Item 2)
  - Undergraduate and Graduate: Fall 1982, 54014 (Box OS 2, Item 3)
  - Undergraduate and Graduate: Spring 1983, 54013 (Box OS 2, Item 4)
  - Undergraduate and Graduate: Summer 1983, 54012 (Box OS 2, Item 5)
  - Undergraduate and Graduate: Fall 1983, 54011 (Box OS 2, Item 6)
  - Undergraduate and Graduate: Spring 1984, 54010 (Box OS 2, Item 7)
  - Undergraduate and Graduate: Summer 1984, 54009 (Box OS 2, Item 8)
  - Undergraduate and Graduate: Fall 1984, 54008 (Box OS 2, Item 9)
  - Undergraduate and Graduate: Spring 1985, 54007 (Box OS 2, Item 10)
  - Undergraduate and Graduate: Summer 1985, 54006 (Box OS 2, Item 11A)
  - Undergraduate and Graduate: Fall 1985, 54005 (Box OS 2, Item 11B)
  - Undergraduate and Graduate: Spring 1986, 54004 (Box OS 2, Item 11C)
  - Undergraduate and Graduate: Summer 1986, 54003 (Box OS 2, Item 11)
  - Undergraduate and Graduate: Fall 1986, 54002 (Box OS 2, Item 12)
  - Undergraduate and Graduate: Spring 1987, 54001 (Box OS 2, Item 13)
  - Undergraduate and Graduate: Summer 1987, 54000 (Box OS 2, Item 14)
  - Undergraduate and Graduate: Fall 1987, 53999 (Box OS 2, Item 15)
  - Undergraduate and Graduate: Spring 1988, 53998 (Box OS 2, Item 16)
  - Undergraduate and Graduate: Summer 1988, 53997 (Box OS 2, Item 17)
  - Undergraduate and Graduate: Fall 1988, 53996 (Box OS 2, Item 18)
  - Undergraduate and Graduate: Spring 1989, 53995 (Box OS 2, Item 19)
  - Undergraduate and Graduate: Summer 1989, 53994 (Box OS 2, Item 20)
  - Undergraduate and Graduate: Fall 1989, 53993 (Box OS 2, Item 21A)
  - Undergraduate and Graduate: Spring 1990, 53992 (Box OS 2, Item 21B)
  - Undergraduate and Graduate: Summer 1990, 53991 (Box OS 2, Item 22)
  - Undergraduate and Graduate: Fall 1990, 53990 (Box OS 2, Item 23)
  - Undergraduate and Graduate: Spring 1991, 53989 (Box OS 2, Item 24)
  - Undergraduate and Graduate: Summer 1991, 53988 (Box OS 2, Item 25A)
  - Summer Session for Teachers: Summer 1992, 53987 (Box OS 2, Item 25B)
  - Summer Session for Teachers: Summer 1993, 53986 (Box OS 2, Item 25C)
  - Undergraduate and Graduate: Fall 1994, 53985 (Box OS 2, Item 26)
  - Undergraduate and Graduate: Spring 1995, 53984 (Box OS 2, Item 27)
  - Undergraduate and Graduate: Summer 1995, 53983 (Box OS 2, Item 28)
  - Undergraduate and Graduate: Fall 1995, 53982 (Box OS 2, Item 29)
  - Undergraduate and Graduate: Spring 1996, 53981 (Box OS 2, Item 30A)
  - Undergraduate and Graduate: Summer 1996, 53980 (Box OS 2, Item 30B)
  - Undergraduate and Graduate: Fall 1996, 53979 (Box OS 2, Item 30C)
  - Undergraduate and Graduate: Spring 1997, 53978 (Box OS 2, Item 31)
  - Undergraduate and Graduate: Summer 1997, 53977 (Box OS 2, Item 32)
  - Undergraduate and Graduate: Fall 1997, 53976 (Box OS 2, Item 33)
  - Undergraduate and Graduate: Spring 1998, 53975 (Box OS 2, Item 34)
  - Undergraduate and Graduate: Summer 1998, 53974 (Box OS 2, Item 35)
  - Undergraduate and Graduate: Fall 1998, 53973 (Box OS 2, Item 36)
  - Undergraduate and Graduate: Spring 1999, 53972 (Box OS 2, Item 37)
  - Undergraduate and Graduate: Summer 1999, 53971 (Box OS 2, Item 38)
  - Undergraduate and Graduate: Fall 1999, 53970 (Box OS 2, Item 39)
- Yearbooks, 53888
  Missing yearbooks for years: 1907, 1908, 1909, 1911, 1912, 1913, 1914, 1915, 1916, 1917, 1918, 1919, 1920, 1921, 1922, 1923, 1925, 1926, 1927, 1928, 1929, 1930, 1931, 1932, 1933, 1934, 1936, 1937, 1938, 1939, 2003, 2004, 2005, & 2007
  - Normalities, 1906; 53960 (Item 1)
    1 copy
  - Classbook Danbury Normal School, 1910; 53959 (Item 2)
  - The Anchor Yearbook Danbury State Normal School, 1924; 53958 (Item 3)
  - The Penningian Danbury Normal School, 1935; 53957 (Item 4)
  - Yearbook of the Danbury State Teachers College, 1940; 53956 (Item 5)
  - The Gravure Yearbook, 1941; 53955 (Item 6)
  - The Blue and White Danbury State Teachers College, 1942; 53954 (Item 7)
  - Dee Tee Cee Forty Three, 1943; 53953 (Item 8)
  - The Coin, 1944; 53952 (Item 9)
    4 copies
  - Pahquioque, 1945; 53951 (Item 10)
  - Pahquioque, 1946; 53950 (Item 11)
  - Pahquioque, 1947; 53949 (Item 12)
  - Pahquioque, 1948; 53948 (Item 13)
    5 copies
  - Pahquioque, 1949; 53947 (Item 14)
  - Pahquioque, 1950; 53946 (Item 15)
  - Pahquioque, 1951; 53945 (Item 16)
  - Pahquioque, 1952; 53944 (Item 17)
  - Pahquioque, 1953; 53943 (Item 18)
  - Pahquioque, 1954; 53942 (Item 19)
  - Pahquioque, 1955; 53941 (Item 20)
  - Pahquioque, 1956; 53940 (Item 21)
  - Pahquioque, 1957; 53939 (Item 22)
  - Pahquioque, 1958; 53938 (Item 23)
  - Pahquioque, 1959; 53937 (Item 24)
  - Pahquioque, 1960; 53936 (Item 25)
  - Reactions…The Yearbook of Danbury State College, 1961; 53935 (Item 26)
  - Principles of Uncertainty, 1962; 53934 (Item 27)
  - Danbury State College I Wish You Could've Been There, 1963; 53933 (Item 28)
  - Danbury State College One Man, 1964; 53932 (Item 29)
    7 copies
  - Yearbook supplement, 1964; 53931 (Item 30)
  - Pahquioque, 1965; 53930 (Item 31)
  - Pahquioque, 1966; 53929 (Item 32)
    8 copies
  - Spring Weekend Supplement, 1966; 53928 (Item 33)
  - Pahquioque, 1967; 53927 (Item 34)
  - Western Connecticut State College, 1968; 53926 (Item 35)
    6 copies
  - Western Connecticut State College, 1969; 53925 (Item 36)
  - Images of 1970, 53924 (Item 37)
  - "Yearbook", 1971; 53923 (Item 38)
  - "Yearbook", 1972; 53922 (Item 39)
  - "Yearbook", 1973; 53921 (Item 40)
  - "Yearbook", 1974; 53920 (Item 41)
  - "Yearbook", 1975; 53919 (Item 42)
  - Wesconn, 1976; 53918 (Item 43)
  - Westconn, 1977; 53917 (Item 44)
  - Westconn, 1978; 53916 (Item 45)
  - West Conn, 1979; 53915 (Item 46)
    9 copies
  - Westconn, 1980; 53914 (Item 47)
    12 copies
  - Westconn, 1981; 53913 (Item 48)
  - Western, 1982; 53912 (Item 49)
    13 copies
  - Western Connecticut State University, 1983; 53911 (Item 50)
  - Western Connecticut State University, 1984; 53910 (Item 51)
    14 copies
  - Western Connecticut State University, 1985; 53909 (Item 52)
  - Western Connecticut State University, 1986; 53908 (Item 53)
    18 copies
  - Western Connecticut State University, 1987; 53907 (Item 54)
  - Western Connecticut State University, 1988; 53906 (Item 55)